[
	{
		"quizTitle": "Articles",
		"category": "English",
		"quizContent": [
            {
               "question": "...... apple a day keeps the doctor away.",
               "correct_answer": "An",
               "incorrect_answer":["The","Is", "A"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Can you please help me pick out ...... birthday present for my father? ",
                "correct_answer": "a",
                "incorrect_answer":["an","is", "the"]
             },
             {
                "question": ".... President of the United States will be visiting Australia next week.",
                "correct_answer": "The",
                "incorrect_answer":["An","Are", "A"]
             },
             {
                "question": "I want to buy .... laptop computer next week.",
                "correct_answer": "a",
                "incorrect_answer":["A","the", "an"]
             },
             {
                "question": "Can you please go to ..... grocery store on Fifth Street and buy 2 cartons of milk?",
                "correct_answer": "the",
                "incorrect_answer":["The","an", "a"]
             }
        ]
	},
    {
		"quizTitle": "Human Body",
		"category": "Science",
		"quizContent": [
            {
               "question": "Which organ in the human body pumps blood?",
               "correct_answer": "Heart",
               "incorrect_answer":["Intestines","Liver", "Kidney"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these organs is used for breathing?",
                "correct_answer": "Lungs",
                "incorrect_answer":["Nose","Legs", "Liver"]
             },
             {
                "question": "Which of these organs can grow back again if some of it is removed?",
                "correct_answer": "Liver",
                "incorrect_answer":["Kidney","Heart", "Brain"]
             },
             {
                "question": "Which of these organs is vital for thinking?",
                "correct_answer": "Brain",
                "incorrect_answer":["Heart","Legs", "Lungs"]
             },
             {
                "question": "Which of these sense organs helps with vision?",
                "correct_answer": "Eyes",
                "incorrect_answer":["Ears","Tounge", "Nose"]
             },
             {
                "question": "Which of these sense organs is vital for your sense of smell?",
                "correct_answer": "Nose",
                "incorrect_answer":["Eats","Eyes", "Tongue"]
             },
             {
                "question": "Which of these sense organs helps us to hear?",
                "correct_answer": "Ears",
                "incorrect_answer":["Nose","Mouth", "Eyes"]
             },
             {
                "question": "Which of these sense organs helps us to swallow food?",
                "correct_answer": "Tongue",
                "incorrect_answer":["Ears","Nose", "Eyes"]
             },
             {
                "question": "Which of these organs helps to purify blood?",
                "correct_answer": "Kidneys",
                "incorrect_answer":["Heart","Lungs", "Alveoli"]
             },
             {
                "question": "Which of these sense organs covers our skeletal system?",
                "correct_answer": "Skin",
                "incorrect_answer":["Mouth","Heart", "Stomach"]
             }
        ]
	}
]